export const quiz = {
  totalQuestions: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Which of the following is not a real paint name?",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "English Muffin",
          swatch: "A7850G",
          code: "#F5EFE4",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "Canvas White",
          swatch: "C6840H",
          code: "#F1EFE7",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "Dream White",
          swatch: "C4880H",
          code: "#F4F2E8",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "Dove Soul",
          swatch: "A4380G",
          code: "#EFE8E1",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question:
        "Which of the following Duck Egg colors are not found on Crown Paints?",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "Classic Duck Egg",
          swatch: "K9370U",
          code: "#94A8AA",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "Duck Egg",
          swatch: "L4267Y",
          code: "#97B1C4",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "Duck Egg Blue",
          swatch: "L2590Y",
          code: "#B5D0D4",
        },

        {
          id: 4,
          name: "Soft Duck Egg ",
          swatch: "H9580X",
          code: "#83D0C8",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Which is not a colour created by Chat GPT?",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "Sizzling Saffron",
          swatch: "A7850G",
          code: "#FFA500",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "Cinnamon Zest ",
          swatch: "FFA500",
          code: "#D2691E",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "Turmeric Tango",
          swatch: "FFA500",
          code: "#FFD700",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "Mustard Jar",
          swatch: "B4542Q",
          code: "#E7BD65",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "When was Hempel established?",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "1915",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "1916",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "1912",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "1908",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is the correct the spelling of Rune's Surname?",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "Steenborg",
          code: "#f5f2f3",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "Steenburg",
          code: "#f5f2f3",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "Steenberg",
          code: "#f5f2f3",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "Stenberg",
          code: "#f5f2f3",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Which of the following is called Revolution?",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "",
          code: "#646B6E",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "",
          code: "#4697C9",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "",
          code: "#D06171",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "",
          code: "#fFDF85",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Which of these is a brand Hempel stocks?",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "Hempadynamic",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "Hemplife",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "Hempayatch",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "Hempafire",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question:
        "Since 2010 How many children have benefitted from projects ran by the Hempel Foundation",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "285,000",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "300,000",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "305,000",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "385,000",
          code: "#ffffff",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Which color has the name Go Green",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "",
          swatch: "",
          code: "#978767",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "",
          swatch: "",
          code: "#176559",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "",
          swatch: "",
          code: "#21645D",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "",
          swatch: "",
          code: "#686043",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Which is the real Hempel Blue",
      answers: [
        {
          id: 1,
          name: "",
          swatch: "",
          code: "#005ba0",
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          name: "",
          swatch: "",
          code: "#0018a0",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          name: "",
          swatch: "",
          code: "#0033a0",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          name: "",
          swatch: "",
          code: "#000ba0",
        },
      ],
      correctAnswer: 3,
    },
  ],
};
